[
  {
    "question": "What is 25 * 4?",
    "correct_answer": "100"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the next number of the sequence 11, 14, 19, 26, ____?",
    "correct_answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which number logically follows the series 2, 4, 7, 4, 12, 4, ___?",
    "correct_answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the missing number in the sequence 20, 17, 22, ____, 24?",
    "correct_answer": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which number is the next 4 numbers in this pattern 9, 18, 36, ___, ___, ___, ___?",
    "correct_answer": "72, 144, 288, 576"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these numbers is not a prime number? 163, 199, 100, 67",
    "correct_answer": "100"
  },
  {
    "question": "If 4+(x) is 11 and 6+(x) is 13, what does x equal to?",
    "correct_answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the place value of the 7 in the number 567986?",
    "correct_answer": "7,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fraction is the biggest: \u2155, 3/5, \u00bd, 4/7?",
    "correct_answer": "3/5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the missing number in the series 1, 2, 4, __, 8, 10?",
    "correct_answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the missing number in the series 200, 190, ___, 170, 160?",
    "correct_answer": "180"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the missing number in '?' place\u2026 3, 2, 9, ?, 15, 14, 21?",
    "correct_answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the odd number: 2, 202, 385, 150, 148?",
    "correct_answer": "385"
  },
  {
    "question": "Solve -30x + (-10x) = 0",
    "correct_answer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 1.62 / 3?",
    "correct_answer": "0.54"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 140+96+25?",
    "correct_answer": "261"
  },
  {
    "question": "10+(80/2) Equal to?",
    "correct_answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "The product of 315x0x47x18 is?",
    "correct_answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 150% of 4751?",
    "correct_answer": "7,126.5"
  },
  {
    "question": "If y(x-3) = z then x =?",
    "correct_answer": "z/y + 3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following fractions is equal to 7/10: 7/12, 21/30, 56/13, 21/60?",
    "correct_answer": "21/30"
  }
]